<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Friends Quizz</string>
    <string name="category">Choose your Category</string>
    <string name="whois">Most likely to</string>
    <string name="deep">Deep</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="met">About me</string>
    <string name="plus">Friendship Test</string>
    <string name="random">Random</string>
    <string name="lines">Who would you choose to...?</string>
    <string name="add_question">New Question</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="ifyou">What if...?</string>
    <string name="challengeTitle">Daily Challege</string>

    <string name="whoisQuestion">whoisQuestion</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion">deepQuestion</string>
    <string name="metQuestion">metQuestion</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion">knowQuestion</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion">linesQuestion</string>
    <string name="ifYouQuestion">selectQuestion</string>
    <string name="whoisTest">whois</string>
    <string name="debate">Discussion topics</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion">debateQuestion</string>
    <string name="select">What do you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion">selectQuestions</string>
    <string name="helpBack">Back</string>
    <string name="helpNext">Next</string>

    <!-- Whosis -->
    <string name="whoisQuestion1">Who is most likely to answer your call at midnight?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion2">Who is most likely to feel at home in your house?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion3">Who would get along well with everyone\'s parents?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion4">Who is most likely to organize a surprise party for someone?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion5">Who is most likely to be a great professional chauffeur?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion6">Who is most likely to handmake your birthday gift?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion7">Who is most likely to make someone laugh when they are sad?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion8">Who is most likely to bake you a cake for your birthday?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion9">Who is most likely to come up with nicknames for everyone?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion10">Who is most likely to reply to a text or email immediately?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion11">Who is most likely to lend you their favorite book?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion12">Who is most likely to forget to return a borrowed book?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion13">Who is most likely to stay up all night looking at their phone?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion14">Who is most likely to know all the office gossip?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion15">Who is most likely to fall asleep during a meeting?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion16">Who is most likely to keep an important secret?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion17">Who is most likely to forget a birthday?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion18">Who is most likely to spend their entire paycheck on clothes or shoes?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion19">Who is most likely to drop their new phone and break it?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion20">Who is most likely to forget the lunch they packed?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion21">Who is most likely to miss a flight?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion22">Who is most likely to give the best Secret Santa gift?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion23">Who is most likely to have their pet on their lap during a meeting or call?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion24">Who is most likely to forget to mute their microphone during a meeting or conference call?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion25">Who is most likely to say something important while muted on a call?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion26">Who is most likely to have 20 tabs open on their desktop?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion27">Who is most likely to cheat in a board game?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion28">Who is most likely to hit the snooze button 5 times on the alarm?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion29">Who is most likely to sleep through the alarm?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion30">Who is most likely to spend hours reading celebrity gossip?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion31">Who is most likely to cheer you up on a difficult day?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion32">Who is most willing to help solve a problem?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion33">Who is most likely to make you forget your problems for a while?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion34">Who is most likely to have an ear available to listen?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion35">Who is most likely to become a great leader in the future?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion36">Who is most likely to save the day when things go wrong?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion37">Who is most likely to say good things about you behind your back?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion38">Who is most likely to inspire you?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion39">Who is most likely to bring out the best in the people they meet?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion40">Who is most likely to have an impact on history?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion41">Who is most likely to offer moral support to a friend?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion42">Who is most likely to give you the perfect gift?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion43">Who is most likely to help a stranger?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion44">Who is most likely to perform a random act of kindness?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion45">Who is most likely to make new friends in a new place?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion46">Who is most likely to coach others in some way?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion47">Who is most likely to eat cold pizza?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion48">Who is most likely to eat breakfast for dinner?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion49">Who is most likely to forget their wallet when they go out to eat?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion50">Who is most likely to talk in a movie theater during a show?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion51">Who is most likely to scold others for talking in a movie theater during a show?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion52">Who is most likely to complete a public challenge that leads to an arrest?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion53">Who is most likely to use all the blankets when they sleep?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion54">Who is most likely to be the travel planner for family or friends\' vacations?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion55">Who is most likely to binge-watch an entire show in one day?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion56">Who is most likely to forget to buy groceries for the week?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion57">Who is most likely to eat all the popcorn during a movie?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion58">Who is most likely to scream for help when they see a spider?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion59">Who is most likely to kill a spider when they see one?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion60">Who is most likely to move to a cabin in the woods?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion61">Who is most likely to do different voices for the characters when reading a book aloud?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion62">Who is most likely to get an embarrassing tattoo?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion63">Who is most likely to cheat on an exam?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion64">Who is most likely to pee in the shower?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion65">Who is most likely to never change their sheets?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion66">Who is most likely to be late?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion67">Who often misses class?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion68">Who is most likely to talk back to a teacher?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion69">Who is most likely to become an interior designer?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion70">Who is most likely to respond to a text three weeks later?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion71">Who is most likely to live abroad?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion72">Who is most likely to become a doctor?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion73">Who is most likely to give the best advice?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion74">Who is most likely to start a business?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion75">Who is most likely to go vegan?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion76">Who is most likely to travel to space?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion77">Who is most likely to stay calm during a big storm?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion78">Who is most likely to drop everything to help a stranger?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion79">Who is most likely to paint a famous work of art?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion80">Who is most likely to leave without saying goodbye?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion81">Who is most likely to drop their laptop?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion82">Who is most likely to teach you something new?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion83">Who is most likely to become a teacher?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion84">Who is most likely to travel the world?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion85">Who is most likely to start a podcast?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion86">Who is most likely to give the best hug?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion87">Who is most likely to write a handwritten letter?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion88">Who is most likely to write a book?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion89">Who is most likely to plan the group\'s vacations?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion90">Who is most likely to start fights?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion91">Who is most likely to apologize first?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion92">Who is most likely to organize the most fun outings?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion93">Who is most likely to tell the same story over and over again?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion94">Who cooks the best in the group?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion95">Who is most likely to eat from someone else\'s plate?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion96">Who falls asleep the earliest?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion97">Who is the one who always proposes outings?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion98">Who is the group\'s psychologist?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion99">Who is the one who always misses the gatherings?</string>

    <!-- Deep -->
    <string name="deepQuestion1">One a scale of 1 to 100, how well do you know yourself?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion2">Are you more mental or emotional?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion3">Do you find it easy to accept help to achieve your dreams?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion4">Do you regret not having done something in life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion5">What makes you most nervous?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion6">What is your relationship with your parents like?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion7">Were you punished a lot when you were little?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion8">What has been the best period of your life? And the worst?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion9">What nightmares have caused you the coldest sweats?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion10">How would you describe yourself?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion11">What do you value most in a friendship?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion12">From 1 to 100, How much do you know yourself?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion13">What does our friendship mean to you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion14">How do you like to be comforted or cheered up when you are sad or angry?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion15">What is the moment in your life that has tested you the most?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion16">Do you regret anything? If so, what?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion17">If you had all the courage possible to do what scares you the most, what would you do?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion18">What thoughts make it difficult for you to sleep at night?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion19">What stresses you out the most in life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion20">What is the worst decision you have made?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion21">Who was your first friend? Are they still in your life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion22">What object has the most sentimental value to you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion23">How can I be a better friend to you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion24">If you could change one thing about yourself, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion25">What makes you cry the most?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion26">Do you have any strange quirks that I don\'t know about?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion27">Who is the most important person in your life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion28">What was the first thing you thought of me when we first met?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion29">What really makes you lose your temper?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion30">Do you find it easy to trust someone?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion31">Could you forgive someone who has been unfaithful if you found out that they still love you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion32">Who has had a decisive influence on you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion33">What do you like most about me?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion34">What makes me different from other people?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion35">When was the last time you felt sad?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion36">Why did your last relationship end?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion37">What makes you feel guilty?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion38">What qualities do you value most in someone?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion39">How would you describe me?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion40">Is there something you think others think of you that isn\'t true?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion41">What four adjectives describe how you are?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion42">What do you like most about yourself?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion43">What has disappointed you the most in a friendship?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion44">What are you most proud of in this life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion45">What do you regret?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion46">How do you deal with anxiety?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion47">How do you deal with stress?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion48">What type of people make you feel most insecure or shy?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion49">Would you hire a friend in your company?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion50">Would you rather have a great innate talent for an activity, or the ability to work hard?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion51">What is your main irrational fear?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion52">On a scale of 1 to 100, how stressed do you feel?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion53">On a scale of 1 to 100, where is your self-esteem?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion54">On a scale of 1 to 100, how much anxiety do you currently feel?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion55">On a scale of 1 to 100, how much do you trust yourself?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion56">What are you most afraid of?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion57">What are your biggest priorities in life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion58">Who do you most resemble in your family?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion59">How do you deal with disappointments?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion60">What do you most feel like doing every day?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion61">What has been your proudest moment?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion62">Have you lost someone close?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion63">Are you spiritual?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion64">Do you think you are honest with yourself?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion65">Who would narrate an audiobook about your life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion66">If you could change something in your life immediately, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion67">What is your greatest skill?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion68">What hobby have you always wanted to pursue?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion69">How do you hope people perceive you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion70">What makes you happiest?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion71">Have you ever lost a best friend?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion72">What makes you feel most seen?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion73">Do you think keeping secrets is bad?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion74">When do you feel most free?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion75">Do you think holding grudges is good?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion76">What is the craziest thing you have done for someone else and why did you do it?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion77">Are you a pessimist or an optimist?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion78">When was the last time you cried?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion79">What is the most impressive place you have visited in person?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion80">What do you think people automatically assume when they first meet you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion81">What do you wish you knew when you were younger?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion82">What is the best bad decision you have made in your life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion83">What would you try if you knew you wouldn\'t fail?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion84">When was the last time you tried something new?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion85">Who do you compare yourself to the most?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion86">Is there an important lesson you have learned the hard way?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion87">What do you wish you could spend more time on?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion88">Is there something you know you are wrong about?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion89">What is your biggest blind belief?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion90">What has been the most decisive moment of your life so far?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion91">Has your deepest fear ever come true?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion92">Does everyone deserve a second chance?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion93">What is the strangest encounter you have had?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion94">What makes you feel most alive?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion95">When was the last time you felt lost?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion96">What do you like most about yourself?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion97">What is the question that scares you the most?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion98">What do you like most about your personality?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion99">What have you done as an adult that your younger self would be proud of?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion100">Tell me about a day when you were happy</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion101">Where would you like to travel again?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion102">What gives you goosebumps?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion103">What is your love language?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion104">What form of personal expression have you not dared to explore?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion105">What memory makes you smile instantly?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion106">What do you think you will feel nostalgic about in 30 years?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion107">Do you have any childhood memory that will always be with you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion108">How do you feel best supported in difficult times?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion109">What would you like people to understand better about you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion110">What do you like most about our friendship? What would you like to improve?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion111">What is your favourite memory of us together?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion112">Do you recharge by being around other people or spending time alone?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion113">In your life, who would you say loves you unconditionally?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion114">Where do you go to feel closer to yourself?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion115">What is the kindest thing someone has ever said to you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion116">What song makes you smile instantly?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion117">If you could go back and relive one day without changing it, which day would you choose?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion118">What memory do you hold onto when you need to feel warmth and security?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion119">Who is the person that always makes you feel understood and accepted?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion120">What moment in your life made you feel truly loved for who you are?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion121">What is a small act of kindness that you still remember?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion122">When do you feel most at peace with yourself and the world around you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion123">If you could tell your younger self something, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion124">What smell instantly brings back good memories?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion125">What always makes you feel at home, no matter where you are?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion126">Who has been a constant source of support in your life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion127">What piece of advice has stayed with you over the years?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion128">Tell me something I did that you didn\'t like but never told me.</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion129">Tell me something you really think should change.</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion130">What is the question you\'ve never asked me?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion131">Have you ever felt our friendship was one-sided, and if so, when?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion132">Is there something you haven\'t told me that you think I should know?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion133">Have you ever felt hurt by something I said or did, and we never talked about it?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion134">Is there a part of your life that you think I don\'t understand or recognize?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion135">Is there any belief or value I hold that you completely disagree with but haven\'t mentioned?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion136">Have you ever felt judged by me, and if so, about what?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion137">Is there a moment when you felt I wasn\'t there for you when you needed me most?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion138">Do you feel there is a part of you that you can\'t express around me?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion139">Have you ever felt envious or resentful towards me, and why?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion140">Is there something in our relationship that you fear losing?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion141">Is there something you\'ve done for me that you feel I haven\'t appreciated enough?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion142">Have you ever been afraid to be completely honest with me? Why?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion143">Is there something you wish you had done differently in our friendship?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion144">Have you ever felt excluded from a plan I made?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion145">Is there an opinion or advice I\'ve given that secretly bothered you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion146">Have I ever asked you for something that made you feel uncomfortable or pressured?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion147">Have you ever felt belittled by something I said or did?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion148">Is there an expectation you think I have of you that weighs on you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion149">Is there something you\'d like to tell me but fear it might change our relationship?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion150">Have you ever felt I made a decision that affected our friendship without consulting you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion151">Is there a promise you feel I haven\'t kept in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion152">Is there an aspect of your life you\'d like to share more with me but feel uncomfortable doing so?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion153">Have you ever felt I took our friendship for granted?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion154">Is there a misunderstanding that we haven\'t resolved yet?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion155">Would you like us to be more honest with each other, even if it means having difficult conversations?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion156">Have you ever felt I avoided talking about something important to you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion157">Is there an attitude or behavior of mine that has disappointed you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion158">Have you ever doubted the sincerity of my intentions or words?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion159">Do you feel there is an emotional distance between us that we haven\'t addressed?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion160">Would you like there to be more transparency or vulnerability in our friendship?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion161">Have you ever felt I didn\'t listen to what you really wanted to tell me?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion162">Is there something from your past that you think I should know but never told me?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion163">Have you ever felt underestimated in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion164">Is there a situation where you wish I had defended you and I didn\'t?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion165">Have you ever felt uncomfortable sharing your problems with me?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion166">Is there an occasion when you felt I didn\'t value your feelings?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion167">Is there something you think I am unable to accept about you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion168">Have you ever felt ignored or overlooked in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion169">Would you like us to spend more time together or connect in a different way?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion170">Have I ever broken your trust without knowing it?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion171">Have you ever felt emotionally distant from me and didn\'t tell me?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion172">Is there a characteristic of mine that you find difficult to handle or understand?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion173">Is there a piece of advice I gave you that you wish I hadn\'t?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion174">Have you ever felt overwhelmed by my problems or situations?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion175">Is there something you think I haven\'t asked you but you wish I would?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion176">Have you ever felt you were competing with me for something?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion177">Is there an aspect of our relationship that you would like to improve or change?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion178">Have you ever felt uncomfortable sharing your achievements with me?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion179">If you could change one thing about our relationship, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion180">What do you think is the most important thing I have learned from you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion181">What do you think would improve our communication?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion182">What do you think is the biggest difference between our personalities?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion183">Would you like us to share more about our future plans?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion184">Do you feel our friendship has evolved or changed over time? How?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion185">What do you think is what binds us together as friends the most?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion186">If you had to describe our friendship in one word, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion187">Have you ever felt I disrespected you by how I behaved in public?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion188">What is something you would like us to do more together that we haven\'t done yet?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion189">What has been the biggest challenge we have overcome together in our friendship?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion190">What do you think we could learn from each other if we opened up more?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion191">What is something you\'ve always wondered about me but never dared to ask?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion192">If you had to describe a moment when you felt especially close to me, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion193">Is there an aspect of my life that you feel I don\'t share enough with you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion194">Would you like us to do more activities outside our comfort zone?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion195">Have you ever felt I put other friends above you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion196">If I moved to another city tomorrow, what do you think would be the hardest part about our friendship at a distance?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion197">Is there something you think I don\'t appreciate enough about you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion198">What do you think has been the biggest misunderstanding between us so far?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion199">If you had to choose one thing that always makes you smile about our friendship, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion200">What do you think is what I admire most about you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion201">What would you like us to remember together in 10 years?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion202">Have you ever felt I didn\'t share your successes the way you would have liked?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion203">Would you like us to talk more about our emotions and feelings?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion204">What has been the best advice you\'ve given me that you think I\'ve ignored?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion205">Would you like me to be more open about my worries and fears?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion206">What do you think we could learn if we had a deeper conversation about our differences?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion207">If you could change one thing from the past in our relationship, what would it be and why?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion208">Is there a topic we never talk about that you\'d like to discuss?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion209">Have you ever felt uncomfortable asking me for help?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion210">What is something you value in other friendships that you\'d like to see more of in ours?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion211">What do you think is what most differentiates our friendship from others you have?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion212">Have I ever disappointed you without knowing it? How?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion213">Have you ever had doubts about our friendship? What caused them?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion214">Do you think there is something we should have talked about a long time ago but keep avoiding?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion215">Is there a conversation you would like to revisit because you feel it wasn\'t resolved?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion216">What would you like me to do to show you that I value our friendship more than I already do?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion217">What is something you think I didn\'t thank you enough for when you did it for me?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion218">If you had to choose a place that represents our friendship, what would it be and why?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion219">Is there a habit I have that you find curious or strange?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion220">Have you ever felt you had to change something about yourself to fit in better with me?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion221">Is there a difficult conversation you\'d like to have but don\'t know how to start?</string>

    <!-- Met -->
    <string name="metQuestion1">What makes you most nervous?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion2">How is your relationship with your parents?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion3">Were you punished a lot when you were little?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion4">What has been the best time of your life? And the worst?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion5">What nightmares have given you the coldest sweats?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion6">How would you describe yourself?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion7">What does our friendship mean to you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion8">How do you like to be comforted or cheered up when you\'re sad or angry?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion9">What is the moment in your life that has tested you the most?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion10">If you had all the courage possible to do what scares you the most, what would you do?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion11">What stresses you out the most in life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion12">Who was your first friendship? Is it still in your life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion13">What object holds the most sentimental value for you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion14">Who is the most important person in your life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion15">Do you find it easy to trust someone?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion16">Who has had a decisive influence on you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion17">What qualities do you value most in someone?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion18">What four adjectives describe who you are?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion19">What do you like most about yourself?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion20">What has disappointed you most in a friendship?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion21">What are you most proud of in this life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion22">Would you prefer to have a great innate talent for an activity, or the ability to work hard at it?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion23">Do you recharge by being around other people or by spending time alone?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion24">What is your ideal plan to unwind on vacation?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion25">Who is your favourite TikTok content creator? And on Instagram?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion26">Do you have any phobias?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion27">What is your favourite board game?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion28">What is your favourite colour?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion29">What does your dream job look like?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion30">What TV series do you watch whenever you need cheering up?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion31">What is your favourite movie of the last few months?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion32">What is the series you\'ve enjoyed the most?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion33">What always makes you laugh?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion34">Are you more of a beach person or a mountain person?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion35">What is the longest trip you\'ve taken?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion36">What emoji do you use the most in your WhatsApp chats?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion37">Are you an early bird or a night owl?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion38">Do you believe in the infinity of the Universe?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion39">Do you believe in God or any divine force?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion40">Would you like to change jobs?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion41">What is the last book you read?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion42">And the last movie you watched?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion43">What is your favorite video game?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion44">Do you value culture?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion45">What are your hidden talents?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion46">What is the book you always want to read but haven\'t yet?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion47">What has been your longest-lasting relationship?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion48">Do you prefer cold or hot weather?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion49">What song would you like to sing loudly in a karaoke?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion50">Which country would you like to visit next?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion51">How do you rate yourself sexually?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion52">What did you do as a young person that you wouldn\'t dare to do now, not even as a joke?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion53">What is the book that has most impacted your life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion54">How would you change society for the better?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion55">If you could travel back in time to change one thing about your life, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion56">What does normalcy mean to you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion57">Do you consider yourself more introverted or extroverted?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion58">When was the last time you broke someone\'s heart?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion59">Do you believe in second chances?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion60">What story would you tell a child to make them fall asleep?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion61">Do you think lies, in certain situations, can be justified?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion62">Have you ever sympathised with or agreed with a fictional villain?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion63">What would you immediately like to learn right now if you had the chance?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion64">What is your definition of good and evil?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion65">Who is the nicest person you\'ve ever met?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion66">Do you follow a life philosophy?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion67">If you could change the world, what would you change?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion68">What does life mean to you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion69">If you could access a crystal ball that predicts only one thing about your future, what would you like to know?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion70">What question do you want people to ask you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion71">If you were to die tomorrow, what would you do today?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion72">Do you have any routines you repeat every time the day starts?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion73">Do you have any routine that you repeat every day?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion74">Did you dream of anything when you were little that you have now achieved?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion75">How do you like to spend your free time?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion76">What would you do tomorrow if you won a million euros today?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion77">What was the happiest day of your life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion78">What is the first thing you do in the morning?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion79">What surprises people most about you when they first meet you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion80">What excites you most about your job?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion81">Which country fascinates you the most?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion82">What is at the top of your wishlist?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion83">What would your perfect day look like?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion84">What do you most enjoy doing with your friends?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion85">If you could freeze your life at a specific age, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion86">What is your greatest achievement in life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion87">Do you cook often? What do you like to cook?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion88">Would you like to be famous or be remembered in some way?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion89">What do you most appreciate about this life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion90">What is your most cherished childhood memory?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion91">What is something you would never joke about?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion92">When you were little, what did you want to be when you grew up?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion93">What hobbies would you like to try?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion94">What scares you the most?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion95">Where did you go on vacation as a child?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion96">What is the first thing you examine when looking for a new apartment or house?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion97">How was your first day at school?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion98">If you could interview someone, who would it be?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion99">What does freedom mean to you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion100">What was your least favourite subject in school?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion101">What do you consider to be a good salary?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion102">Which famous person would you swap with for 24 hours?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion103">Which friend would you trust the most with a job involving brute force?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion104">Do you believe in aliens?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion105">What did you dream about last night?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion106">If you could only eat one thing for the rest of your life, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion107">What was the worst date you\'ve ever experienced?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion108">What is your favourite dessert?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion109">What is your most recurring dream?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion110">What great invention would you like to exist before you die?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion111">When can someone be considered to have cheated on their partner?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion112">What food or drink is never missing from your fridge?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion113">If reincarnation existed, what would you like to be reincarnated as?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion114">What would you change about yourself if you could relive your life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion115">Would you be part of the volunteers who would go live with extraterrestrials?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion116">What phrase would you like to have on your tombstone?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion117">Do you sleep with or without pyjamas?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion118">If you could have dinner with a historical figure, who would it be?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion119">What would you eat for your last meal?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion120">What is your favourite joke?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion121">What is the greatest pain you have felt?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion122">To what extent do you like or hate your job?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion123">How are you going to spend your next vacation?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion124">What will be your next haircut?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion125">What do you miss most about your childhood?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion126">Do you want to have children?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion127">Would you like to adopt a child?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion128">In which country would you have liked to be born?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion129">What is the weirdest thing you wanted to be when you grew up?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion130">What was the first photo you posted on Instagram?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion131">Where is the weirdest place you would get a tattoo?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion132">Where do you see yourself in 5 years? And in 10? And in 15?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion133">Who was your favourite teacher in childhood?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion134">What do you like most about your job?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion135">What is your favourite word?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion136">Have you ever been in a serious relationship?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion137">What is your favourite word?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion138">What is the most spontaneous thing you have ever done?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion139">How old were you when you had your first kiss? How did it go?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion140">Who else do you admire in this world?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion141">What motivates you to get up every morning?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion142">What are the 3 things that bother you the most?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion143">Would you tattoo your partner\'s name?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion144">What is your ideal weekend plan?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion145">What would you ask for if you were going to be granted a single wish?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion146">What has been the best thing that has happened to you in life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion147">What is the biggest crazy thing you have done for love?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion148">Have you ever cheated?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion149">Have you ever been in love with several people at the same time?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion150">Do you prefer sporadic or long-term relationships?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion151">Do you enjoy doing sports?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion152">What would your dream vacation look like?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion153">What is the best thing that happened to you today?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion154">What are you terrible at?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion155">What scares you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion156">Do you like to know what is happening in other countries?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion157">What does infidelity mean to you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion158">Do you believe that friendships are forever?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion159">Can you trust a friend who never suggests making plans together?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion160">Which adjective do you think best describes you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion161">In what area of your life do you think your creative side is most evident?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion162">What does love mean to you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion163">Do you consider that it takes you a long time to show your fears and vulnerabilities to a friend?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion164">Can you play any musical instrument that no one knows about?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion165">Can you play any musical instrument?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion166">Can you do any impressions of famous characters?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion167">Do you have any artistic talents, such as painting or drawing, that few people know about?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion168">Are you good at any specific type of dance?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion169">Do you have a knack for solving puzzles or riddles?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion170">Can you speak any language that few people know about?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion171">Do you have any skills in magic or card tricks?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion172">Can you make any kind of art with recycled materials?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion173">Do you have any special culinary talents, like making decorative cakes?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion174">Can you do any tricks with your tongue, such as touching your nose with it?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion175">Are you good at any type of writing, such as poetry or stories?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion176">Do you have any skills in gardening or plant care?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion177">Can you juggle different objects?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion178">Are you able to bend parts of your body in unusual ways?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion179">Do you have any singing talent that no one knows about?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion180">Can you make any sounds with your mouth that others can\'t?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion181">Are you good at any type of strategy or board games?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion182">Do you have a knack for sewing or knitting?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion183">Can you do any kind of crafts, such as wood carving?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion184">Do you have any talent for acting or theatre?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion185">Are you able to solve Rubik\'s cubes quickly?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion186">Do you have any talent for organising trips or itineraries?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion187">Are you good at any type of strategy game, such as chess?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion188">Can you do any acrobatics or contortionism?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion189">Are you good at any type of DIY or carpentry?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion190">Can you do any cartoon voices?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion191">Do you have a knack for decorating cakes or cookies?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion192">Can you do any type of weaving, such as macram?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion193">Are you able to play a song on an unusual instrument?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion194">Do you have any talent for photography?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion195">Can you do any kind of artistic makeup?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion196">Do you have a knack for graphic design or digital illustration?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion197">Are you good at any type of exotic or cultural dance?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion198">Can you build complex things with LEGO or similar?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion199">Do you have a knack for lettering or calligraphy?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion200">Are you able to choreograph a dance routine?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion201">Can you do any kind of animation or stop motion?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion202">Do you have any talent for scriptwriting or playwriting?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion203">Are you good at any type of water sports?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion204">Can you make any kind of costume or cosplay?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion205">Do you have a knack for restoring old furniture?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion206">Are you able to identify local birds or plants?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion207">Can you do any kind of miniature building?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion208">Do you have any talent for video editing?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion209">Are you good at any type of embroidery or cross-stitch?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion210">Can you do any kind of glass or ceramic crafts?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion211">Do you have a knack for interior decoration?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion212">Are you able to write with both hands?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion213">Can you do any kind of sculpture, whether with clay or recycled materials?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion214">Do you have any talent for storytelling?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion215">Are you good at any type of extreme sport, such as climbing?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion216">Can you do any kind of juggling with fire or knives?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion217">Do you have a knack for fashion design or clothing making?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion218">Are you able to identify constellations in the night sky?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion219">Can you do any kind of shadow theatre?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion220">Do you have any talent for organising and planning events?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion221">Are you good at any type of ornamental calligraphy?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion222">Can you do any kind of electronic repair?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion223">Do you have a knack for special effects makeup?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion224">Are you able to compose music or write songs?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion225">Can you do any kind of ice or sand sculpture?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion226">Do you have any talent for teaching or tutoring in specific subjects?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion227">Are you good at any type of alternative therapy, such as massage or Reiki?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion228">Can you do any kind of art restoration?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion229">Do you have a knack for dream analysis or interpretation?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion230">Are you able to do any kind of scientific experiments at home?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion231">Can you make any kind of puppets or marionettes?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion232">Do you have any talent for creating games or puzzles?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion233">Are you good at any type of animal training?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion234">Can you choreograph any kind of fight or martial arts routine?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion235">Do you have a knack for body painting or temporary tattoos?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion236">Are you able to do any kind of nail art?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion237">Can you do any kind of craft with papier-mch?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion238">Do you have any talent for making jewellery?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion239">Are you good at any type of winter sport, such as skiing or snowboarding?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion240">Can you do any kind of mosaic or stained glass work?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion241">Do you have a knack for restoring old books?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion242">Are you able to do any kind of model building?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion243">Can you do any kind of raised embroidery?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion244">Do you have any talent for film or theatre criticism?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion245">Are you good at any type of ballroom dancing?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion246">Can you do any kind of blacksmithing or forging work?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion247">Do you have a knack for home brewing or winemaking?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion248">Are you able to design and build gardens or landscapes?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion249">Can you do any kind of classic car restoration?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion250">Do you have any talent for food sculpture, such as fruit carving?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion251">Are you good at any type of mural painting?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion252">Can you choreograph any kind of ice skating routine?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion253">Do you have a knack for tattoo design?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion254">Are you able to do any kind of plumbing or electrical work?</string>


    <!-- Know -->
    <string name="knowQuestion1">What is my favourite colour?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion2">What is my favourite book?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion3">Do I prefer coffee or tea?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion4">What is my favourite movie?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion5">Who is my favourite band/singer?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion6">Do I prefer dogs or cats?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion7">Do I prefer early mornings or late nights?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion8">What is my favourite hobby?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion9">What is my favourite drink?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion10">Do I prefer to travel by plane or train?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion11">What is my favourite animal?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion12">Do I prefer a rainy day or a sunny day?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion13">What is my favourite ice cream flavour?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion14">When is my birthday?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion15">Do I prefer physical books or e-books?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion16">What quickly puts me in a bad mood?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion17">What is my favourite fruit?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion18">What instantly makes me happy?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion19">What is my favourite genre of literature?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion20">Do I prefer white chocolate or dark chocolate?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion21">What do I value most in a friendship?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion22">What activity relaxes me the most?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion23">What is my favourite animated series?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion24">What do I hate doing the most?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion25">What is my favourite Disney movie?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion26">Do I prefer pizza over pasta?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion27">Have I lived in more than one city?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion28">Am I an organized person?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion29">Do I have any tattoos?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion30">Do I like video games?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion31">Do I have any hobbies related to art?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion32">Do I like football?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion33">Do I like amusement parks?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion34">Do I like documentaries?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion35">Do I like beer?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion36">Do I prefer non-fiction books over fiction?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion37">Do I like gardening?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion38">Do I prefer cars over motorcycles?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion39">Have I participated in a car race?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion40">Do I prefer digital watches over analog ones?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion41">Have I ever visited an art museum?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion42">Have I taken any online courses?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion43">Do I prefer bicycles over cars?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion44">Do I like board games?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion45">Do I like writing?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion46">Do I prefer a long life without love or a short life full of love?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion47">Do I prefer inner peace or professional success?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion48">Do I prefer to forgive easily or hold grudges?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion49">Do I prefer brutal honesty or white lies?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion50">Would I rather have an incredible talent in one specific thing or be good at many things?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion51">Would I rather live in a world without war or a world without diseases?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion52">Do I prefer to have many superficial friends or a few true friends?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion53">Do I prefer to make decisions based on logic or emotion?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion54">Would I rather work in something I love for little money or in something I hate for a lot of money?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion55">Do I prefer to live in the present or plan for the future?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion56">Would I rather be completely free or absolutely secure?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion57">Would I prefer to pursue my dreams even if I fail or never try and never know?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion58">Would I prefer to live a life without technology or a life without friends?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion59">Would I prefer to find true love or a suitcase with ten million dollars?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion60">Would I prefer to experience great physical pain or great emotional pain?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion61">Would I prefer to be a brilliant but lonely person or an average person with an active social life?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion62">Would I prefer to help a needy friend even if it harms me or protect myself and not help?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion63">Would I prefer to live without music or without movies?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion64">Would I prefer to have a stable but boring job or an exciting but unstable job?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion65">Would I prefer to never feel sadness again or never feel physical pain again?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion66">Would I prefer to fight for a cause I believe in or live a quiet life without getting involved?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion67">Would I prefer to seek revenge or practice forgiveness?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion68">Would I prefer to spend a night talking with someone I admire or with someone I love?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion69">Would I prefer to succeed in an area I\'m not passionate about or fail in something I\'m passionate about?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion70">Would I prefer to live a life without regrets or without expectations?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion71">Would I prefer to have a complicated but passionate love relationship or a simple relationship without passion?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion72">Would I prefer to be a leader with many enemies or a follower loved by all?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion73">Would I prefer to have the chance to fully know myself or fully know someone else?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion74">Would I prefer to listen to my heart or my mind?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion75">Would I prefer to have everyone\'s respect or the love of a few?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion76">Would I prefer to always be told the truth or be protected by a lie?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion77">Would I prefer to be known for my intelligence or for my kindness?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion78">Would you prefer to never experience happiness or never experience love?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion79">Would I prefer to be unable to lie or unable to trust?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion80">Would I prefer to be remembered for one incredible thing or for a lifetime of kindness?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion81">Would I prefer to know the truth even if it hurts or live in blissful ignorance?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion82">Would I prefer to be able to love deeply but be vulnerable or never love and be invulnerable?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion83">Would I prefer to live in a place where it\'s always day or where it\'s always night?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion84">Would I prefer to live a life without romantic love or a life without friendship?</string>
    <!-- Lines -->
    <string name="linesQuestion1">Who would you choose to survive on a desert island with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion2">Who would you choose to organize your wedding?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion3">Who would you choose to take care of your pets?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion4">Who would you choose to be your travel companion?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion5">Who would you choose to cook your favourite dinner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion6">Who would you choose to make you laugh on a sad day?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion7">Who would you choose to help you move?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion8">Who would you choose to be your personal trainer?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion9">Who would you choose to decorate your house?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion10">Who would you choose to accompany you to a party?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion11">Who would you choose to help you study for an exam?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion12">Who would you choose to give you fashion advice?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion13">Who would you choose to be your business partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion14">Who would you choose to be your confidant?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion15">Who would you choose to care for your children?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion16">Who would you choose to go on a date with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion17">Who would you choose to sing at your wedding?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion18">Who would you choose to design your tattoo?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion19">Who would you choose to be your mentor?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion20">Who would you choose to solve a mystery?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion21">Who would you choose to play a prank on?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion22">Who would you choose to organize a surprise party?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion23">Who would you choose to give a speech at your wedding?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion24">Who would you choose to design your house?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion25">Who would you choose to go to a concert with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion26">Who would you choose to defend you in court?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion27">Who would you choose to be your teammate in a trivia game?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion28">Who would you choose to write a book with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion29">Who would you choose to accompany you to an important dinner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion30">Who would you choose to give you a makeover?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion31">Who would you choose to manage your finances?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion32">Who would you choose to teach you a new language?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion33">Who would you choose to design your clothes?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion34">Who would you choose to plan your holidays?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion35">Who would you choose to help you build something?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion36">Who would you choose to take care of your garden?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion37">Who would you choose to be your gym buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion38">Who would you choose to help you get over a breakup?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion39">Who would you choose to give you relationship advice?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion40">Who would you choose to help you solve a math problem?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion41">Who would you choose to create artwork with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion42">Who would you choose to go shopping with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion43">Who would you choose to be your roommate?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion44">Who would you choose for a movie marathon?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion45">Who would you choose for an extreme adventure?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion46">Who would you choose to play video games with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion47">Who would you choose to prepare a picnic with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion48">Who would you choose for a board game night?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion49">Who would you choose to care for your grandparents?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion50">Who would you choose to accompany you to the doctor?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion51">Who would you choose to write an essay with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion52">Who would you choose to go to an amusement park with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion53">Who would you choose to be your dance partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion54">Who would you choose to help you learn to drive?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion55">Who would you choose to be your bodyguard?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion56">Who would you choose to be your fishing buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion57">Who would you choose to design your website?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion58">Who would you choose to take care of your home while you\'re away?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion59">Who would you choose to prepare a barbecue with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion60">Who would you choose to be your tour guide in a new city?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion61">Who would you choose to be your study partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion62">Who would you choose to be your therapist?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion63">Who would you choose to take care of you when you\'re sick?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion64">Who would you choose to organize a bachelor(ette) party?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion65">Who would you choose to be your hiking companion?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion66">Who would you choose to direct your funeral?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion67">Who would you choose to take you Christmas shopping?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion68">Who would you choose to help you organize a charity event?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion69">Who would you choose to be your partner in an escape room?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion70">Who would you choose to teach you to play a musical instrument?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion71">Who would you choose to design your company logo?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion72">Who would you choose to be your dance partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion73">Who would you choose to help you clean your house?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion74">Who would you choose to write an important letter with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion75">Who would you choose to help you exercise?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion76">Who would you choose to plan a romantic surprise?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion77">Who would you choose to help you fix something broken?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion78">Who would you choose to accompany you to a job interview?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion79">Who would you choose to be your race partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion80">Who would you choose to be your reading marathon partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion81">Who would you choose to help you overcome a phobia?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion82">Who would you choose to give you a gift?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion83">Who would you choose to teach you to dance?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion84">Who would you choose to do crafts with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion85">Who would you choose to be your companion for night walks?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion86">Who would you choose to help you solve a puzzle?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion87">Who would you choose to be your work colleague?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion88">Who would you choose to be your life partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion89">Who would you choose to do a school project with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion90">Who would you choose to take care of your siblings?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion91">Who would you choose to go on a road trip with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion92">Who would you choose to help you move to a new city?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion93">Who would you choose to help you get through a bad day?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion94">Who would you choose to be your volunteer work partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion95">Who would you choose to make a documentary with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion96">Who would you choose to go hiking with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion97">Who would you choose to decorate a cake with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion98">Who would you choose to be your academic advisor?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion99">Who would you choose to teach you to swim?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion100">Who would you choose to be your shopping buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion101">Who would you choose to help you write a speech?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion102">Who would you choose to be your personal photographer?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion103">Who would you choose to give you a relaxing massage?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion104">Who would you choose to be your astronomy study partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion105">Who would you choose to organize your birthday party?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion106">Who would you choose to design your garden?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion107">Who would you choose to accompany you to a museum?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion108">Who would you choose to help you learn to ski?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion109">Who would you choose to be your cycling buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion110">Who would you choose to help you create a blog?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion111">Who would you choose to help you get better at a sport?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion112">Who would you choose to help you find a new hobby?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion113">Who would you choose to be your running partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion114">Who would you choose to decorate your office?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion115">Who would you choose to help you learn to paint?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion116">Who would you choose to be your gardening buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion117">Who would you choose to teach you meditation?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion118">Who would you choose to help you overcome stage fright?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion119">Who would you choose to help you find the perfect gift?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion120">Who would you choose to be your theatre partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion121">Who would you choose to give you a history lesson?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion122">Who would you choose to be your diving buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion123">Who would you choose to help you train your pet?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion124">Who would you choose to be your swimming buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion125">Who would you choose to teach you pottery?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion126">Who would you choose to be your camping buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion127">Who would you choose to be your train travel companion?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion128">Who would you choose to help you design your clothes?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion129">Who would you choose to be your skating partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion130">Who would you choose to help you learn to surf?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion131">Who would you choose to be your skiing companion?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion132">Who would you choose to help you plan a children\'s party?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion133">Who would you choose to be your wine tasting partner?</string>

    <!-- Debate -->
    <string name="debateQuestion1">Would you lie to protect a friend?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion2">Would you steal to feed your family?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion3">Would you let a stranger take the blame for something you did?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion4">Would you save someone you love at the cost of many unknown lives?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion5">Would you betray a friend to save your job?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion6">Would you help a friend cover up a crime?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion7">Would you accept a bribe to do something you consider immoral?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion8">Would you let someone suffer if it benefitted you?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion9">Would you use confidential information to gain an advantage?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion10">Would you lie about your qualifications to get a job?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion11">Would you hide a medical mistake you made if it didn\t affect the patient\s health?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion12">Would you turn in a colleague doing something illegal if it endangered your career?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion13">Would you rather save an elderly person or a child in a fire?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion14">Would you be willing to betray your country if it meant saving many lives?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion15">Would you take a well-paid job that goes against your ethical principles?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion16">Would you risk your life to save a stranger?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion17">Would you let someone you hate win if it benefitted the majority?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion18">Would you be willing to physically harm someone if it was the only way to save your life?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion19">Would you hide information that could ruin someone\s life if it wasn\t illegal?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion20">Would you help someone who has wronged you in the past if they truly needed it?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion21">Would you abandon your family to pursue a dream?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion22">Would you lie in a relationship to keep the peace?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion23">Would you let an innocent person be punished for a crime they didn\t commit to protect your loved one?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion24">Would you sell confidential information to pay off an urgent debt?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion25">Would you be willing to do something you consider immoral to get your dream job?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion26">Would you turn in a friend if you knew they committed a serious crime?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion27">Would you accept a large sum of money to lie in an official statement?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion28">Would you rather tell the truth and hurt someone or lie to protect their feelings?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion29">Would you risk your life to save an endangered animal?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion30">Would you make a decision that benefits a few but harms many?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion31">Would you leave your partner if you discovered they committed a crime in the past?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion32">Would you be willing to face great personal risk to fight for a just cause?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion33">Would you hide information that could harm a friend if it was in their best interest?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion34">Would you lie to protect the reputation of someone you respect?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion35">Would you risk your life to save someone you barely know?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion36">Would you accept money to keep a harmful secret?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion37">Would you betray someone if it guaranteed your family\s wellbeing?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion38">Would you accept a tempting offer if it meant hurting someone you don\t know?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion39">Would you be willing to break the law to help a loved one?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion40">Would you lie to a friend if you knew the truth would devastate them?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion41">Would you take the blame for something you didn\t do to protect someone else?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion42">Would you be willing to damage your reputation to protect someone you love?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion43">Would you accept a promotion if you knew someone else deserved it more?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion44">Would you let an innocent person be punished if it meant protecting a loved one?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion45">Would you risk your career to fight an injustice at your workplace?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion46">Would you do something illegal if it was the only way to save your life?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion47">Would you lie in a critical situation to save many lives?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion48">Would you sacrifice your principles for a substantial reward?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion49">Would you be willing to forgive someone who has greatly harmed you?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion50">Would you rather save a family member or five strangers in a disaster?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion51">Would you make a decision that benefits your country but harms your family?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion52">Would you risk your freedom to protect someone you love?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion53">Would you accept to do something immoral to gain power and influence?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion54">Would you lie about a friend to avoid legal trouble?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion55">Would you betray someone to save your own life?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion56">Would you let someone suffer an injustice if it was in your best interest?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion57">Would you be willing to compromise your values for love?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion58">Would you hide the truth to avoid an uncomfortable situation?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion59">Would you do something against your principles if it meant saving a life?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion60">Would you rather help a friend in need or a group of strangers?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion61">Would you accept a lucrative job if you knew the company acted immorally?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion62">Would you lie to protect someone\s relationship?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion63">Would you betray your best friend to avoid a major personal loss?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion64">Would you accept a large sum of money to do something you find repugnant?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion65">Would you risk your own happiness for someone else\s wellbeing?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion66">Would you rather be honest and hurt someone or lie to keep the peace?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion67">Would you sacrifice your own happiness to make someone you love happy?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion68">Would you make a difficult decision that benefits the majority but harms a minority?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion69">Would you risk your life to protect an innocent person?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion70">Would you accept an expensive gift from someone you dislike?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion71">Would you be willing to give up something important to you for the good of others?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion72">Would you lie in court to protect a friend?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion73">Would you rather fulfil your duties or follow your heart?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion74">Would you make a decision that benefits your family but harms others?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion75">Would you be willing to betray someone to avoid a major problem?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion76">Would you hide a serious mistake you made if no one else knows about it?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion77">Would you accept an offer that goes against your principles if it benefitted you significantly?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion78">Would you risk your reputation to save a friend?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion79">Would you lie to avoid a major financial loss?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion80">Would you rather help someone you love or a group of strangers?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion81">Would you sacrifice your own comfort to help someone else?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion82">Would you accept a bribe to do something immoral?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion83">Would you be willing to lose something valuable to you for others\ wellbeing?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion84">Would you lie to protect your career?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion85">Would you let someone else take credit for your work to avoid conflict?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion86">Would you make a difficult decision that benefits your community but harms a few?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion87">Would you rather be honest and face the consequences or lie to avoid them?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion88">Would you risk your life to save someone you don\t know?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion89">Would you be willing to forgive a betrayal for the sake of peace?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion90">Would you make a decision that benefits your company but harms other employees?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion91">Would you rather tell the truth and risk a relationship or lie to keep it?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion92">Would you do something you think is wrong if it was for a good cause?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion93">Would you sacrifice your own wellbeing to protect someone you love?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion94">Would you lie to avoid a dangerous situation?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion95">Would you accept an offer that benefits many but harms a few?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion96">Would you rather help a friend in need or a stranger in danger?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion97">Would you make a decision that benefits your community but harms your personal interests?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion98">Would you be willing to betray your principles for a greater cause?</string>
    <string name="debateQuestion99">Would you risk your career to do the right thing?</string>

    <!-- Select -->
    <string name="selectQuestion1">If you could only eat one type of food for the rest of your life, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion2">If you could travel in time, which era would you go to and why?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion3">If you won a million dollars, what would you do first?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion4">If you could live anywhere in the world, where would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion5">If you could be any fictional character, who would you be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion6">If you could change one thing from your past, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion7">If you could meet any person, dead or alive, who would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion8">If you could only listen to one song for the rest of your life, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion9">If you could be invisible for a day, what would you do?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion10">If you could talk to animals, what would you ask your pet?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion11">If you had to choose between flying or being invisible, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion12">If you could have a conversation with your future self, what would you ask?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion13">If you had to choose between never being able to use technology again or living without electricity, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion14">If you could have any job in the world, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion15">If you could change one thing in the world, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion16">If you could only watch one film for the rest of your life, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion17">If you could be an expert in anything, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion18">If you could eliminate one bad habit, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion19">If you could instantly learn a new language, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion20">If you could only have three things on a desert island, what would you take?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion21">If you had to live in a different country for a year, where would you go?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion22">If you could be a celebrity for a day, who would you be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion23">If you could change one thing about the education system, what would you change?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion24">If you had to choose between being very rich but unhappy or having enough money and being happy, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion25">If you could have any athletic ability, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion26">If you could change your name, what name would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion27">If you could only read one book for the rest of your life, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion28">If you had the option to never have to sleep again, would you take it?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion29">If you could live in any historical period, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion30">If you had to choose between being famous but hated or unknown but loved, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion31">If you could swap lives with someone for a day, who would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion32">If you could eliminate one fear from your life, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion33">If you could only use one social network for the rest of your life, which would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion34">If you had to choose between losing all your memories or never being able to make new ones, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion35">If you could be the president of any country, which would you choose and what would you do first?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion36">If you could only have one hobby, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion37">If you could live on any planet, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion38">If you could change one thing about your appearance, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion39">If you could relive one moment of your life, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion40">If you had to choose between always being cold or always being hot, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion41">If you could eliminate one injustice in the world, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion42">If you had to choose between being very intelligent but socially awkward or being average but very sociable, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion43">If you could only use one app on your phone, which would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion44">If you could be a character in any video game, who would you be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion45">If you had to live without one of your senses, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion46">If you could change one thing about society, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion47">If you could know the future, would you want to know it?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion48">If you could have any pet, real or imaginary, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion49">If you had to choose between never watching TV again or never listening to music again, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion50">If you could change one thing about your personality, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion51">If you could live in any book, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion52">If you had to choose between always being honest or always being kind, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion53">If you could be famous in any field, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion54">If you had to choose between being the best at something you hate or being mediocre at something you love, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion55">If you could eliminate one emotion, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion56">If you had to choose between being extremely strong or extremely fast, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion57">If you could bring back a famous person from the dead, who would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion58">If you could change the ending of a film, which would you change?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion59">If you had to choose between living in the city or the countryside, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion60">If you could change your profession right now, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion61">If you had to live without the internet or without a phone, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion62">If you could create a law that everyone had to follow, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion63">If you had to choose between losing the ability to read or the ability to speak, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion64">If you could visit any place in space, where would you go?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion65">If you could have any artistic talent, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion66">If you had to choose between being rich and lonely or poor with many friends, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion67">If you could change one thing about your life, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion68">If you had to choose between being the protagonist in a tragedy or a secondary character in a comedy, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion69">If you could change one important decision from your past, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion70">If you had to choose between being famous for something bad or completely unknown, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion71">If you could live in any climate, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion72">If you had to choose between always being young or living forever, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion73">If you could instantly learn any skill, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion74">If you had to choose between losing your short-term memory or your long-term memory, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion75">If you could be the best at something for a day, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion76">If you had to choose between never having holidays again or working every day at something you love, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion77">If you could be any animal for a day, what would you be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion78">If you had to choose between a boring but well-paid job or an interesting but poorly paid job, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion79">If you could have anything for free for life, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion80">If you had to choose between a perfect but short romantic relationship or a long but imperfect one, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion81">If you could have any superpower for a day, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion82">If you had to choose between being unable to lie or being unable to love, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion83">If you could swap lives with someone for a week, who would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion84">If you had to choose between having all the knowledge in the world or all the money in the world, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion85">If you could live in any film, which would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion86">If you had to choose between being a leader or a follower, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion87">If you could eliminate one global problem, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion88">If you had to choose between living without music or living without art, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion89">If you could have a conversation with your childhood self, what would you say?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion90">If you had to choose between being extremely tall or extremely short, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion91">If you could change the course of history, what would you change?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion92">If you had to choose between being very rich but hated or being loved but poor, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion93">If you could have anything in the world, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion94">If you had to choose between being able to fly or being able to breathe underwater, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion95">If you could live in any city in the world, which would it be?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion96">If you had to choose between never using the internet again or never travelling again, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion97">If you could know the future, would you want to?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion98">If you had to choose between living forever or dying tomorrow, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="selectQuestion99">If you could change one law in your country, what would it be?</string>


    <!-- Challenge -->
    <string name="yesterday">Yesterday</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="tomorrow">Tomorrow</string>

    <string name="d20241019">Enva un mensaje a un amigo con quien no hablas hace tiempo. Pregntale cmo est o invtale un caf.</string>
    <string name="d20241020">Organiza un desayuno con alguien para esta semana.</string>
    <string name="d20241021">Organiza para juntarte a comer con un familiar.</string>
    <string name="d20241022">Invita a alguien a caminar o tomar un caf.</string>
    <string name="d20241023">Comparte una cancin que te guste con un amigo.</string>
    <string name="d20241024">Pregunta a un amigo qu libro o serie te recomendara.</string>
    <string name="d20241025">Haz una lista de personas con las que te gustara reconectar. Escrbele a una.</string>
    <string name="d20241026">Investiga sobre algo que te haya preguntado un amigo y envale lo que encontraste.</string>
    <string name="d20241027">Comparte algo positivo en tus redes sociales. (Puede ser por privado).</string>
    <string name="d20241028">Enva un mensaje de gratitud a alguien que haya tenido un impacto en tu vida. (Puede ser una foto y sticker tambin).</string>
    <string name="d20241029">Organiza un rincn de tu casa.</string>
    <string name="d20241030">Compra ese artculo que siempre olvidas.</string>
    <string name="d20241031">Haz una lista de pendientes pequeos y resuelve al menos uno.</string>
    <string name="d20241101">Prepara tu desayuno favorito para maana.</string>
    <string name="d20241102">Anota una idea o proyecto que siempre tengas en mente.</string>
    <string name="d20241103">Escribe un objetivo pequeo para esta semana.</string>
    <string name="d20241104">Limpia la bandeja de entrada de tu correo electrnico.</string>
    <string name="d20241105">Haz algo que llevas posponiendo desde hace das.</string>
    <string name="d20241106">Ponte ropa que hace mucho no utilizas.</string>
    <string name="d20241107">Planifica tu da de maana en 5 minutos.</string>
    <string name="d20241108">Mira un tutorial introductorio de algo que te gustara aprender.</string>
    <string name="d20241109">Escribe sobre un tema que te interese, aunque sea solo para vos.</string>
    <string name="d20241110">Lee 3 pginas de un libro.</string>
    <string name="d20241111">Aprende una palabra nueva en otro idioma.</string>
    <string name="d20241112">Escucha un podcast corto.</string>
    <string name="d20241113">Dibuja algo, como una flor o una figura geomtrica.</string>
    <string name="d20241114">Investiga sobre un tema curioso que siempre te ha intrigado.</string>
    <string name="d20241115">Dedica 10 minutos a aprender algo relacionado con tu trabajo o estudios.</string>
    <string name="d20241116">Descubre un canal de YouTube educativo y mira un video.</string>
    <string name="d20241117">Aprende una receta sencilla y preprala.</string>
    <string name="d20241118">Gurdate una lista de reproduccin sobre algo que te gustara aprender.</string>
    <string name="d20241119">Escucha una cancin que te levante el nimo.</string>
    <string name="d20241120">Dedica 5 minutos a estirar tus msculos.</string>
    <string name="d20241121">Date una ducha relajante escuchando msica tranquila.</string>
    <string name="d20241122">Desconctate del celular por 30 minutos.</string>
    <string name="d20241123">Piensa en 3 cosas por las que te sientas agradecido hoy.</string>
    <string name="d20241124">Da un paseo corto al aire libre.</string>
    <string name="d20241125">Tmate 10 minutos para tomar una bebida que disfrutes (t, caf, jugo).</string>
    <string name="d20241126">Ordena algo de tu habitacin antes de acostarte.</string>
    <string name="d20241127">Medita 5 minutos.</string>
    <string name="d20241128">Ve a dormir 30 minutos antes de lo habitual.</string>
</resources>