<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Questions</string>
    <string name="category">Game Modes</string>
    <string name="whois">Most likely to</string>
    <string name="deep">Deep</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="met">About me</string>
    <string name="plus">Friendship Test</string>
    <string name="random">Random</string>
    <string name="lines">Who would you choose to...?</string>
    <string name="add_question">New Question</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion">whoisQuestion</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion">deepQuestion</string>
    <string name="metQuestion">metQuestion</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion">knowQuestion</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion">linesQuestion</string>
    <string name="whoisTest">whois</string>

    <!-- Whosis -->
    <string name="whoisQuestion1">Who is most likely to answer your call at midnight?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion2">Who is most likely to feel at home in your house?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion3">Who would get along well with everyone\'s parents?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion4">Who is most likely to organize a surprise party for someone?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion5">Who is most likely to be a great professional chauffeur?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion6">Who is most likely to handmake your birthday gift?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion7">Who is most likely to make someone laugh when they are sad?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion8">Who is most likely to bake you a cake for your birthday?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion9">Who is most likely to come up with nicknames for everyone?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion10">Who is most likely to reply to a text or email immediately?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion11">Who is most likely to lend you their favorite book?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion12">Who is most likely to forget to return a borrowed book?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion13">Who is most likely to stay up all night looking at their phone?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion14">Who is most likely to know all the office gossip?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion15">Who is most likely to fall asleep during a meeting?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion16">Who is most likely to keep an important secret?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion17">Who is most likely to forget a birthday?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion18">Who is most likely to spend their entire paycheck on clothes or shoes?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion19">Who is most likely to drop their new phone and break it?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion20">Who is most likely to forget the lunch they packed?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion21">Who is most likely to miss a flight?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion22">Who is most likely to give the best Secret Santa gift?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion23">Who is most likely to have their pet on their lap during a meeting or call?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion24">Who is most likely to forget to mute their microphone during a meeting or conference call?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion25">Who is most likely to say something important while muted on a call?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion26">Who is most likely to have 20 tabs open on their desktop?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion27">Who is most likely to cheat in a board game?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion28">Who is most likely to hit the snooze button 5 times on the alarm?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion29">Who is most likely to sleep through the alarm?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion30">Who is most likely to spend hours reading celebrity gossip?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion31">Who is most likely to cheer you up on a difficult day?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion32">Who is most willing to help solve a problem?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion33">Who is most likely to make you forget your problems for a while?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion34">Who is most likely to have an ear available to listen?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion35">Who is most likely to become a great leader in the future?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion36">Who is most likely to save the day when things go wrong?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion37">Who is most likely to say good things about you behind your back?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion38">Who is most likely to inspire you?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion39">Who is most likely to bring out the best in the people they meet?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion40">Who is most likely to have an impact on history?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion41">Who is most likely to offer moral support to a friend?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion42">Who is most likely to give you the perfect gift?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion43">Who is most likely to help a stranger?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion44">Who is most likely to perform a random act of kindness?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion45">Who is most likely to make new friends in a new place?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion46">Who is most likely to coach others in some way?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion47">Who is most likely to eat cold pizza?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion48">Who is most likely to eat breakfast for dinner?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion49">Who is most likely to forget their wallet when they go out to eat?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion50">Who is most likely to talk in a movie theater during a show?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion51">Who is most likely to scold others for talking in a movie theater during a show?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion52">Who is most likely to complete a public challenge that leads to an arrest?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion53">Who is most likely to use all the blankets when they sleep?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion54">Who is most likely to be the travel planner for family or friends\' vacations?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion55">Who is most likely to binge-watch an entire show in one day?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion56">Who is most likely to forget to buy groceries for the week?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion57">Who is most likely to eat all the popcorn during a movie?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion58">Who is most likely to scream for help when they see a spider?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion59">Who is most likely to kill a spider when they see one?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion60">Who is most likely to move to a cabin in the woods?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion61">Who is most likely to do different voices for the characters when reading a book aloud?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion62">Who is most likely to get an embarrassing tattoo?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion63">Who is most likely to cheat on an exam?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion64">Who is most likely to pee in the shower?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion65">Who is most likely to never change their sheets?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion66">Who is most likely to be late?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion67">Who often misses class?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion68">Who is most likely to talk back to a teacher?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion69">Who is most likely to become an interior designer?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion70">Who is most likely to respond to a text three weeks later?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion71">Who is most likely to live abroad?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion72">Who is most likely to become a doctor?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion73">Who is most likely to give the best advice?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion74">Who is most likely to start a business?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion75">Who is most likely to go vegan?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion76">Who is most likely to travel to space?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion77">Who is most likely to stay calm during a big storm?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion78">Who is most likely to drop everything to help a stranger?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion79">Who is most likely to paint a famous work of art?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion80">Who is most likely to leave without saying goodbye?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion81">Who is most likely to drop their laptop?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion82">Who is most likely to teach you something new?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion83">Who is most likely to become a teacher?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion84">Who is most likely to travel the world?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion85">Who is most likely to start a podcast?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion86">Who is most likely to give the best hug?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion87">Who is most likely to write a handwritten letter?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion88">Who is most likely to write a book?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion89">Who is most likely to plan the group\'s vacations?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion90">Who is most likely to start fights?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion91">Who is most likely to apologize first?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion92">Who is most likely to organize the most fun outings?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion93">Who is most likely to tell the same story over and over again?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion94">Who is most likely to cancel an outing?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion95">Who is most likely to eat from someone else\'s plate?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion96">Who falls asleep the earliest?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion97">Who is the one who always proposes outings?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion98">Who is the group\'s psychologist?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion99">Who is the one who always misses the gatherings?</string>
    <string name="whoisQuestion100">Who cooks the best in the group?</string>
    <!-- Deep -->
    <string name="deepQuestion1">Are you more mental or emotional?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion2">Are you more mental or emotional?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion3">Do you find it easy to accept help to achieve your dreams?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion4">Do you regret not having done something in life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion5">What makes you most nervous?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion6">What is your relationship with your parents like?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion7">Were you punished a lot when you were little?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion8">What has been the best period of your life? And the worst?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion9">What nightmares have caused you the coldest sweats?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion10">How would you describe yourself?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion11">What do you value most in a friendship?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion12">When was the last time you cried in front of someone else?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion13">What does our friendship mean to you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion14">How do you like to be comforted or cheered up when you are sad or angry?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion15">What is the moment in your life that has tested you the most?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion16">Do you regret anything? If so, what?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion17">If you had all the courage possible to do what scares you the most, what would you do?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion18">What thoughts make it difficult for you to sleep at night?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion19">What stresses you out the most in life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion20">What is the worst decision you have made?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion21">Who was your first friend? Are they still in your life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion22">What object has the most sentimental value to you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion23">How can I be a better friend to you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion24">If you could change one thing about yourself, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion25">What makes you cry the most?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion26">Do you have any strange quirks that I don\'t know about?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion27">Who is the most important person in your life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion28">What was the first thing you thought of me when we first met?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion29">What really makes you lose your temper?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion30">Do you find it easy to trust someone?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion31">Could you forgive someone who has been unfaithful if you found out that they still love you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion32">Who has had a decisive influence on you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion33">What do you like most about me?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion34">What makes me different from other people?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion35">When was the last time you felt sad?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion36">Why did your last relationship end?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion37">What makes you feel guilty?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion38">What qualities do you value most in someone?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion39">How would you describe me?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion40">Is there something you think others think of you that isn\'t true?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion41">What four adjectives describe how you are?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion42">What do you like most about yourself?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion43">What has disappointed you the most in a friendship?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion44">What are you most proud of in this life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion45">What do you regret?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion46">How do you deal with anxiety?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion47">How do you deal with stress?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion48">What type of people make you feel most insecure or shy?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion49">Would you hire a friend in your company?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion50">Would you rather have a great innate talent for an activity, or the ability to work hard?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion51">What is your main irrational fear?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion52">On a scale of 1 to 100, how stressed do you feel?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion53">On a scale of 1 to 100, where is your self-esteem?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion54">On a scale of 1 to 100, how much anxiety do you currently feel?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion55">On a scale of 1 to 100, how much do you trust yourself?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion56">What are you most afraid of?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion57">What are your biggest priorities in life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion58">Who do you most resemble in your family?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion59">How do you deal with disappointments?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion60">What do you most feel like doing every day?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion61">What has been your proudest moment?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion62">Have you lost someone close?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion63">Are you spiritual?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion64">Do you think you are honest with yourself?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion65">Who would narrate an audiobook about your life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion66">If you could change something in your life immediately, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion67">What is your greatest skill?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion68">What hobby have you always wanted to pursue?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion69">How do you hope people perceive you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion70">What makes you happiest?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion71">Have you ever lost a best friend?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion72">What makes you feel most seen?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion73">Do you think keeping secrets is bad?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion74">When do you feel most free?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion75">Do you think holding grudges is good?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion76">What is the craziest thing you have done for someone else and why did you do it?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion77">Are you a pessimist or an optimist?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion78">When was the last time you cried?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion79">What is the most impressive place you have visited in person?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion80">What do you think people automatically assume when they first meet you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion81">What do you wish you knew when you were younger?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion82">What is the best bad decision you have made in your life?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion83">What would you try if you knew you wouldn\'t fail?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion84">When was the last time you tried something new?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion85">Who do you compare yourself to the most?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion86">Is there an important lesson you have learned the hard way?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion87">What do you wish you could spend more time on?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion88">Is there something you know you are wrong about?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion89">What is your biggest blind belief?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion90">What has been the most decisive moment of your life so far?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion91">Has your deepest fear ever come true?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion92">Does everyone deserve a second chance?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion93">What is the strangest encounter you have had?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion94">What makes you feel most alive?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion95">When was the last time you felt lost?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion96">What do you like most about yourself?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion97">What is the question that scares you the most?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion98">What do you like most about your personality?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion99">What have you done as an adult that your younger self would be proud of?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion100">Tell me about a day when you were happy</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion101">Where would you like to travel again?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion102">What gives you goosebumps?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion103">What is your love language?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion104">What form of personal expression have you not dared to explore?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion105">What memory makes you smile instantly?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion106">What do you think you will feel nostalgic about in 30 years?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion107">Do you have any childhood memory that will always be with you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion108">How do you feel best supported in difficult times?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion109">What would you like people to understand better about you?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion110">What do you like most about our friendship? What would you like to improve?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion111">What is your favourite memory of us together?</string>
    <string name="deepQuestion112">Do you recharge by being around other people or spending time alone?</string>
    <!-- Met -->
    <string name="metQuestion1">Are you more mental or emotional?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion2">Do you find it easy to accept help to achieve your dreams?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion3">Do you regret not doing something in life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion4">What makes you most nervous?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion5">How is your relationship with your parents?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion6">Were you punished a lot when you were little?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion7">What has been the best time of your life? And the worst?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion8">What nightmares have given you the coldest sweats?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion9">How would you describe yourself?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion10">What do you value most in a friendship?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion11">When was the last time you cried in front of someone else?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion12">What does our friendship mean to you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion13">How do you like to be comforted or cheered up when you\'re sad or angry?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion14">What is the moment in your life that has tested you the most?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion15">Do you regret anything? If so, what?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion16">If you had all the courage possible to do what scares you the most, what would you do?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion17">What thoughts keep you from sleeping at night?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion18">What stresses you out the most in life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion19">What is the worst decision you\'ve ever made?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion20">Who was your first friendship? Is it still in your life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion21">What object holds the most sentimental value for you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion22">Who is the most important person in your life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion23">Do you find it easy to trust someone?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion24">Could you forgive someone who has been unfaithful to you if you found out they still love you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion25">Who has had a decisive influence on you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion26">What qualities do you value most in someone?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion27">What four adjectives describe who you are?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion28">What do you like most about yourself?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion29">What has disappointed you most in a friendship?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion30">What are you most proud of in this life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion31">What do you regret?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion32">Would you prefer to have a great innate talent for an activity, or the ability to work hard at it?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion33">Do you recharge by being around other people or by spending time alone?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion34">What is your ideal plan to unwind on vacation?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion35">Who is your favourite TikTok content creator? And on Instagram?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion36">Do you have any phobias?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion37">What is your favourite board game?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion38">What is your favourite colour?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion39">What does your dream job look like?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion40">What TV series do you watch whenever you need cheering up?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion41">Do you have the same breakfast every day or do you alternate?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion42">What is your favourite movie of the last few months?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion43">What is the series you\'ve enjoyed the most?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion44">What is the worst question you\'ve been asked in a job interview?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion45">What always makes you laugh?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion46">Are you more of a beach person or a mountain person?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion47">What is the longest trip you\'ve taken?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion48">What emoji do you use the most in your WhatsApp chats?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion49">Are you an early bird or a night owl?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion50">Do you believe in the infinity of the Universe?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion51">Would you like to meet extraterrestrial life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion52">Do you believe in God or any divine force?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion53">Would you like to change jobs?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion54">What is the last book you read?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion55">And the last movie you watched?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion56">Do you prefer a nightclub or a quiet bar?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion57">Do you value culture?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion58">Which museum would you recommend visiting?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion59">What are your hidden talents?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion60">What is the book you always want to read but haven\'t yet?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion61">What has been your longest-lasting relationship?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion62">Do you prefer cold or hot weather?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion63">What song would you like to sing loudly in a karaoke?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion64">Which country would you like to visit next?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion65">How do you rate yourself sexually?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion66">Do you find it difficult to flirt?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion67">What did you do when you were young that you wouldn\'t dare to do now?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion68">Would you change your life for someone you know?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion69">What is the book that has most impacted your life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion70">How would you change society for the better?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion71">If you could only do one activity for the rest of your life, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion72">If you could travel back in time to change one thing about your life, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion73">What does normalcy mean to you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion74">What would you like to have invented?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion75">Do you consider yourself more introverted or extroverted?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion76">When was the last time you broke someone\'s heart?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion77">Do you believe in second chances?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion78">What story would you tell a child to make them fall asleep?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion79">Do you think lies, in certain situations, can be justified?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion80">Have you ever sympathised with or agreed with a fictional villain?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion81">What would you immediately like to learn right now if you had the chance?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion82">What is your definition of good and evil?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion83">What is the most serious injustice you have suffered or witnessed?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion84">Who is the nicest person you\'ve ever met?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion85">What kind of father or mother would you like to be to your future children?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion86">Do you follow a life philosophy?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion87">If you could change the world, what would you change?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion88">What does life mean to you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion89">If you could access a crystal ball that predicts only one thing about your future, what would you like to know?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion90">What question do you want people to ask you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion91">If you were to die tomorrow, what would you do today?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion92">Do you have any routines you repeat every time the day starts?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion93">What are your priorities right at this moment in your life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion94">Did you dream of anything when you were little that you have now achieved?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion95">How do you like to spend your free time?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion96">What would you do tomorrow if you won a million euros today?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion97">What was the happiest day of your life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion98">What is the first thing you do in the morning?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion99">What surprises people most about you when they first meet you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion100">What excites you most about your job?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion101">Which country fascinates you the most?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion102">What is at the top of your wishlist?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion103">What would your perfect day look like?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion104">What do you most enjoy doing with your friends?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion105">If you could freeze your life at a specific age, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion106">What is your greatest achievement in life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion107">Do you cook often? What do you like to cook?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion108">Would you like to be famous or be remembered in some way?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion109">What do you most appreciate about this life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion110">What is your most cherished childhood memory?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion111">What is something you would never joke about?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion112">When you were little, what did you want to be when you grew up?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion113">What hobbies would you like to try?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion114">What scares you the most?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion115">Where did you go on vacation as a child?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion116">What is the first thing you examine when looking for a new apartment or house?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion117">How was your first day at school?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion118">If you could interview someone, who would it be?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion119">What does freedom mean to you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion120">Who is the most special person in your life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion121">What was your favourite subject in school?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion122">What was your least favourite subject in school?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion123">What do you consider to be a good salary?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion124">Where would you like to live if you weren\'t in this city?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion125">Which famous person would you swap with for 24 hours?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion126">Which friend would you trust the most with a job involving brute force?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion127">Would you prefer to be an expert in one thing or just good at everything?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion128">Do you believe in aliens?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion129">What did you dream about last night?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion130">If you could only eat one thing for the rest of your life, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion131">What was the worst date you\'ve ever experienced?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion132">If you could live in another era, which would it be?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion133">What is your favourite dessert?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion134">What is your most recurring dream?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion135">What great invention would you like to exist before you die?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion136">When can someone be considered to have cheated on their partner?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion137">What food or drink is never missing from your fridge?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion138">If reincarnation existed, what would you like to be reincarnated as?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion139">What would you change about yourself if you could relive your life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion140">Would you be part of the volunteers who would go live with extraterrestrials?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion141">What phrase would you like to have on your tombstone?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion142">Do you sleep with or without pyjamas?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion143">If you could have dinner with a historical figure, who would it be?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion144">What would you eat for your last meal?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion145">What is your favourite joke?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion146">What food would you never try?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion147">What is the greatest pain you have felt?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion148">To what extent do you like or hate your job?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion149">How are you going to spend your next vacation?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion150">What will be your next haircut?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion151">What do you miss most about your childhood?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion152">Do you want to have children?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion153">Would you like to adopt a child?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion154">In which country would you have liked to be born?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion155">What is the weirdest thing you wanted to be when you grew up?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion156">What was the first photo you posted on Instagram?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion157">Where is the weirdest place you would get a tattoo?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion158">Where do you see yourself in 5 years? And in 10? And in 15?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion159">What is the craziest thing you\'ve done in your life?"</string>
    <string name="metQuestion160">Who was your favourite teacher in childhood?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion161">How did your parents meet?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion162">Of all your family members, who do you get along with the best?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion163">What is your favourite hobby?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion164">What do you like most about your job?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion165">What is your favourite word?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion166">What is the best gift you\'ve ever received? Who gave it to you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion167">Have you ever been in a serious relationship?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion168">What is your favourite word?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion169">Have you ever had your heart broken?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion170">What is the most spontaneous thing you have ever done?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion171">How old were you when you had your first kiss? How did it go?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion172">Who else do you admire in this world?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion173">Which country would you recommend for me to travel to?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion174">What motivates you to get up every morning?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion175">What are the 3 things that bother you the most?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion176">Would you tattoo your partner\'s name?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion177">What is your ideal weekend plan?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion178">What would you ask for if you were going to be granted a single wish?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion179">What has been the best thing that has happened to you in life?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion180">What is the biggest crazy thing you have done for love?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion181">Have you ever cheated?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion182">Have you ever been in love with several people at the same time?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion183">Do you prefer sporadic or long-term relationships?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion184">Do you enjoy doing sports?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion185">What would your dream vacation look like?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion186">What is the best thing that happened to you today?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion187">What are you terrible at?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion188">What scares you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion189">Do you like to know what is happening in other countries?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion190">What does infidelity mean to you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion191">What is your greatest virtue and your greatest flaw?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion192">Have you ever confessed your feelings to someone?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion193">Do you believe that friendships are forever?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion194">Can you trust a friend who never suggests making plans together?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion195">What are the three most important values for you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion196">Which adjective do you think best describes you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion197">In what area of your life do you think your creative side is most evident?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion198">What does love mean to you?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion199">At what age do you think you started to become a mature person?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion200">How would you like to be remembered when you are no longer here?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion201">Do you consider that it takes you a long time to show your fears and vulnerabilities to a friend?</string>
    <string name="metQuestion202">Who has influenced you the most in this life?</string>
    <!-- Know -->
    <string name="knowQuestion1">What is my favourite colour?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion2">What is my favourite book?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion3">Do I prefer coffee or tea?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion4">What is my favourite movie?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion5">Who is my favourite band/singer?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion6">Do I prefer dogs or cats?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion7">Do I prefer early mornings or late nights?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion8">What is my favourite hobby?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion9">What is my favourite drink?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion10">Do I prefer to travel by plane or train?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion11">What is my favourite animal?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion12">Do I prefer a rainy day or a sunny day?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion13">What is my favourite ice cream flavour?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion14">When is my birthday?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion15">Do I prefer physical books or e-books?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion16">What quickly puts me in a bad mood?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion17">What is my favourite fruit?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion18">What instantly makes me happy?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion19">What is my favourite genre of literature?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion20">Do I prefer white chocolate or dark chocolate?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion21">What do I value most in a friendship?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion22">What activity relaxes me the most?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion23">What is my favourite animated series?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion24">What do I hate doing the most?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion25">What is my favourite Disney movie?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion26">Do I prefer pizza over pasta?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion27">Have I lived in more than one city?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion28">Am I an organized person?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion29">Do I have any tattoos?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion30">Do I like video games?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion31">Do I have any hobbies related to art?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion32">Do I like football?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion33">Do I like amusement parks?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion34">Do I like documentaries?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion35">Do I like beer?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion36">Do I prefer non-fiction books over fiction?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion37">Do I like gardening?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion38">Do I prefer cars over motorcycles?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion39">Have I participated in a car race?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion40">Do I prefer digital watches over analog ones?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion41">Have I ever visited an art museum?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion42">Have I taken any online courses?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion43">Do I prefer bicycles over cars?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion44">Do I like board games?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion45">Do I like writing?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion46">Do I prefer a long life without love or a short life full of love?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion47">Do I prefer inner peace or professional success?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion48">Do I prefer to forgive easily or hold grudges?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion49">Do I prefer brutal honesty or white lies?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion50">Would I rather have an incredible talent in one specific thing or be good at many things?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion51">Would I rather live in a world without war or a world without diseases?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion52">Do I prefer to have many superficial friends or a few true friends?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion53">Do I prefer to make decisions based on logic or emotion?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion54">Would I rather work in something I love for little money or in something I hate for a lot of money?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion55">Do I prefer to live in the present or plan for the future?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion56">Would I rather be completely free or absolutely secure?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion57">Would I prefer to pursue my dreams even if I fail or never try and never know?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion58">Would I prefer to live a life without technology or a life without friends?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion59">Would I prefer to find true love or a suitcase with ten million dollars?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion60">Would I prefer to experience great physical pain or great emotional pain?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion61">Would I prefer to be a brilliant but lonely person or an average person with an active social life?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion62">Would I prefer to help a needy friend even if it harms me or protect myself and not help?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion63">Would I prefer to live without music or without movies?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion64">Would I prefer to have a stable but boring job or an exciting but unstable job?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion65">Would I prefer to never feel sadness again or never feel physical pain again?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion66">Would I prefer to fight for a cause I believe in or live a quiet life without getting involved?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion67">Would I prefer to seek revenge or practice forgiveness?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion68">Would I prefer to spend a night talking with someone I admire or with someone I love?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion69">Would I prefer to succeed in an area I\'m not passionate about or fail in something I\'m passionate about?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion70">Would I prefer to live a life without regrets or without expectations?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion71">Would I prefer to have a complicated but passionate love relationship or a simple relationship without passion?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion72">Would I prefer to be a leader with many enemies or a follower loved by all?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion73">Would I prefer to have the chance to fully know myself or fully know someone else?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion74">Would I prefer to listen to my heart or my mind?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion75">Would I prefer to have everyone\'s respect or the love of a few?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion76">Would I prefer to always be told the truth or be protected by a lie?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion77">Would I prefer to be known for my intelligence or for my kindness?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion78">Would I prefer to never experience sadness again or never experience love again?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion79">Would I prefer to be unable to lie or unable to trust?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion80">Would I prefer to be remembered for one incredible thing or for a lifetime of kindness?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion81">Would I prefer to know the truth even if it hurts or live in blissful ignorance?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion82">Would I prefer to be able to love deeply but be vulnerable or never love and be invulnerable?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion83">Would I prefer to live in a place where it\'s always day or where it\'s always night?</string>
    <string name="knowQuestion84">Would I prefer to live a life without romantic love or a life without friendship?</string>
    <!-- Lines -->
    <string name="linesQuestion1">Who would you choose to survive on a desert island with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion2">Who would you choose to organize your wedding?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion3">Who would you choose to take care of your pets?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion4">Who would you choose to be your travel companion?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion5">Who would you choose to cook your favourite dinner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion6">Who would you choose to make you laugh on a sad day?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion7">Who would you choose to help you move?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion8">Who would you choose to be your personal trainer?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion9">Who would you choose to decorate your house?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion10">Who would you choose to accompany you to a party?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion11">Who would you choose to help you study for an exam?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion12">Who would you choose to give you fashion advice?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion13">Who would you choose to be your business partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion14">Who would you choose to be your confidant?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion15">Who would you choose to care for your children?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion16">Who would you choose to go on a date with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion17">Who would you choose to sing at your wedding?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion18">Who would you choose to design your tattoo?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion19">Who would you choose to be your mentor?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion20">Who would you choose to save the world?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion21">Who would you choose to solve a mystery?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion22">Who would you choose to play you in a biographical film?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion23">Who would you choose to play a prank with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion24">Who would you choose to organize a surprise party?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion25">Who would you choose to give a speech at your wedding?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion26">Who would you choose to design your house?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion27">Who would you choose to go to a concert with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion28">Who would you choose to defend you in court?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion29">Who would you choose to be your teammate in a trivia game?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion30">Who would you choose to write a book with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion31">Who would you choose to accompany you to an important dinner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion32">Who would you choose to give you a makeover?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion33">Who would you choose to manage your finances?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion34">Who would you choose to teach you a new language?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion35">Who would you choose to design your clothes?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion36">Who would you choose to plan your holidays?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion37">Who would you choose to help you build something?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion38">Who would you choose to take care of your garden?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion39">Who would you choose to be your gym buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion40">Who would you choose to help you get over a breakup?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion41">Who would you choose to give you relationship advice?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion42">Who would you choose to help you solve a math problem?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion43">Who would you choose to create artwork with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion44">Who would you choose to go shopping with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion45">Who would you choose to be your roommate?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion46">Who would you choose for a movie marathon?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion47">Who would you choose for an extreme adventure?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion48">Who would you choose to play video games with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion49">Who would you choose to prepare a picnic with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion50">Who would you choose for a board game night?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion51">Who would you choose to care for your grandparents?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion52">Who would you choose to accompany you to the doctor?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion53">Who would you choose to write an essay with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion54">Who would you choose to go to an amusement park with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion55">Who would you choose to be your dance partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion56">Who would you choose to help you learn to drive?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion57">Who would you choose to be your bodyguard?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion58">Who would you choose to be your fishing buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion59">Who would you choose to design your website?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion60">Who would you choose to take care of your home while you\'re away?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion61">Who would you choose to prepare a barbecue with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion62">Who would you choose to be your tour guide in a new city?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion63">Who would you choose to be your study partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion64">Who would you choose to be your therapist?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion65">Who would you choose to take care of you when you\'re sick?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion66">Who would you choose to organize a bachelor(ette) party?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion67">Who would you choose to be your hiking companion?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion68">Who would you choose to direct your funeral?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion69">Who would you choose to take you Christmas shopping?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion70">Who would you choose to help you organize a charity event?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion71">Who would you choose to be your partner in an escape room?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion72">Who would you choose to teach you to play a musical instrument?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion73">Who would you choose to design your company logo?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion74">Who would you choose to be your hiking partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion75">Who would you choose to be your dance partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion76">Who would you choose to help you clean your house?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion77">Who would you choose to write an important letter with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion78">Who would you choose to help you exercise?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion79">Who would you choose to plan a romantic surprise?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion80">Who would you choose to help you fix something broken?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion81">Who would you choose to accompany you to a job interview?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion82">Who would you choose to be your race partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion83">Who would you choose to be your reading marathon partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion84">Who would you choose to help you overcome a phobia?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion85">Who would you choose to give you a gift?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion86">Who would you choose to be your yoga buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion87">Who would you choose to teach you to dance?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion88">Who would you choose to do crafts with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion89">Who would you choose to be your companion for night walks?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion90">Who would you choose to help you solve a puzzle?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion91">Who would you choose to be your work colleague?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion92">Who would you choose to be your life partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion93">Who would you choose to do a school project with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion94">Who would you choose to take care of your siblings?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion95">Who would you choose to go on a road trip with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion96">Who would you choose to help you move to a new city?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion97">Who would you choose to help you get through a bad day?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion98">Who would you choose to be your volunteer work partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion99">Who would you choose to make a documentary with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion100">Who would you choose to go hiking with?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion101">Who would you choose to decorate a cake with you?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion102">Who would you choose to be your academic advisor?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion103">Who would you choose to teach you to swim?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion104">Who would you choose to be your shopping buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion105">Who would you choose to help you write a speech?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion106">Who would you choose to be your personal photographer?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion107">Who would you choose to give you a relaxing massage?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion108">Who would you choose to be your astronomy study partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion109">Who would you choose to organize your birthday party?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion110">Who would you choose to design your garden?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion111">Who would you choose to accompany you to a museum?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion112">Who would you choose to help you learn to ski?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion113">Who would you choose to be your cycling buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion114">Who would you choose to help you create a blog?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion115">Who would you choose to help you get better at a sport?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion116">Who would you choose to help you find a new hobby?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion117">Who would you choose to be your running partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion118">Who would you choose to decorate your office?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion119">Who would you choose to help you learn to paint?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion120">Who would you choose to be your fishing companion?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion121">Who would you choose to be your gardening buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion122">Who would you choose to teach you meditation?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion123">Who would you choose to be your yoga companion?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion124">Who would you choose to help you overcome stage fright?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion125">Who would you choose to be your mountain hiking companion?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion126">Who would you choose to help you find the perfect gift?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion127">Who would you choose to be your theatre partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion128">Who would you choose to give you a history lesson?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion129">Who would you choose to be your diving buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion130">Who would you choose to help you train your pet?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion131">Who would you choose to be your swimming buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion132">Who would you choose to teach you pottery?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion133">Who would you choose to be your camping buddy?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion134">Who would you choose to be your train travel companion?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion135">Who would you choose to help you design your clothes?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion136">Who would you choose to be your skating partner?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion137">Who would you choose to help you learn to surf?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion138">Who would you choose to be your skiing companion?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion139">Who would you choose to help you plan a children\'s party?</string>
    <string name="linesQuestion140">Who would you choose to be your wine tasting partner?</string>
</resources>